(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
超電波ピース！巡ってまるごとガブッ！と
Super Electromagnetic Peace! Circling around, gobbling it all up!
宇宙（そら）の彼方へ テストで交信Chu！
To the other side of the universe (Sora), communicating with a test Chu!
サイン波で唸らせてる 胸躍る超（スーパー）銀河の音
Making a sine wave hum, a heart-pounding super galactic sound.
（アバンチューるラリーラリー）
(Adventure Rally Rally)
８光年先の未来誰もが求めるウェルネス（8次元まで）飛んじゃって
8 light-years into the future, everyone seeks wellness (up to 8 dimensions), flying away.
地球上そうテクテクテクノロジー 満たされちゃってる（アバンチュールPANICPANIC）
On Earth, with all this tech-tech-technology, we're completely satisfied (Adventure Panic Panic).
あっちゅーまに時代はぐるり廻り宇宙は8周目？
In the blink of an eye, time spins around, is the universe on its 8th lap?
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while for the performance to start.
さぁ時代創造して さぁ次の波へ
Now, create a new era, now, to the next wave.
さぁ無限大の可能性へ乗って
Now, ride on the infinite possibilities.
超電波ピース！ ジャックしてまるごとガブッ！と宇宙（そら）の彼方踊れ踊れ
Super Electromagnetic Peace! Jack it and gobble it all up! Dance, dance to the other side of the universe (Sora).
超電波ピース！ 巡ってまるごとガブッ！と エイトなビートに身をまかせ∞（インフィニティ）の先へ
Super Electromagnetic Peace! Circling around, gobbling it all up! Entrust yourself to the eight-beat and go beyond infinity.
パラレル地球◯（まる）のスター性？ 末広がるダンスダンスダンス
The star quality of a parallel Earth? Spreading out, dance, dance, dance.
まだ見たことない未来を テストで更新Chu！
Updating the future we haven't seen yet with a test Chu!
共鳴する超科学バリ3電波！
Resonating super science, full-strength radio waves!
（アバンチューるラリーラリー）
(Adventure Rally Rally)
飛び込むヘリカルバイノーラル
Diving into helical binaural.
（アバンチューる大発見！）
(Adventure Great Discovery!)
この世に革命と連鎖を 時と宇宙（そら）に打ち放て
Unleash revolution and chains upon this world, upon time and the universe (Sora).
魅せるNewWorld （アバンチュールFunnyFunny）
A captivating New World (Adventure Funny Funny).
1人じゃ行けない所まで ついてきてねルネッサンスYeah
To places I can't go alone, come with me, Renaissance Yeah.
さぁ時代を超えて さぁ次はどこへ
Now, transcend time, now, where to next?
さぁ巡り続ける時を駆けて
Now, racing through the endlessly circling time.
超電波ピース！ 紡いできたキミとのメモリー一緒に見た夢はここに今
Super Electromagnetic Peace! The memories woven with you, the dreams we saw together, are here now.
幕は上がり始めた 永遠の先へ
The curtain has begun to rise, towards eternity.
超電波ピース！ ジャックしてまるごとガブッ！と宇宙（そら）の彼方踊れ踊れ
Super Electromagnetic Peace! Jack it and gobble it all up! Dance, dance to the other side of the universe (Sora).
超電波ピース！ 巡ってまるごとガブッ！と エイトなビートに身をまかせ∞（インフィニティ）の先へ
Super Electromagnetic Peace! Circling around, gobbling it all up! Entrust yourself to the eight-beat and go beyond infinity.
パラレル地球◯（まる）のスター性？ 末広がるダンスダンスダンス
The star quality of a parallel Earth? Spreading out, dance, dance, dance.
まだ見たことない未来をベストde更新Chu！
Updating the future we haven't seen yet with the best Chu!
次元を飛び越えて未踏の可能性へ絶賛更新 Chu！
Leaping across dimensions to unexplored possibilities, updating with praise Chu!
明日もまた同じ
If tomorrow is the same,
朝日が昇るなら
and the morning sun rises again,
もう... 何もいらない
I don't need... anything else.
青く光る夜が
The night glowing in blue,
星空のミラーボール
is a mirror ball in the starry sky.
さあ... 私を照らして
Come now... shine a light on me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to shake the earth with a tap,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away right here.
午前5時の夜明けの街で
In the city at dawn, 5 AM,
なんか一人ぼっちな気分
I feel somewhat all alone.
埋もれてゆくパレット
The palette getting buried,
ぼんやり眺めるベッドで期待してる
I gaze at it vaguely from bed, hoping for
君の足音を
the sound of your footsteps.
触れたくても
Even if I want to touch,
触れられないし
I can't reach you.
運命の赤い
I don't know anything about
糸なんて知らないし
a red string of fate.
それでも君と繋がっていたい
But still, I want to be connected with you.
明るくなる空に
Into the brightening sky,
この想い乗せても
even if I send these feelings...
もう... 何も見えない
I can't see... anything anymore.
灰色に流れる
Floating in the grey,
雲の隙間 差し込む
shining through the gaps in the clouds.
さあ... 他人事なんかもう
Come now... forget about other people's business.
たっぷり深呼吸して
Take a deep, deep breath,
境界線を越える
and cross the boundary line.
明日もまた同じ
If tomorrow is the same,
朝日が昇るなら
and the morning sun rises again,
もう... 何もいらない
I don't need... anything else.
青く光る夜が
The night glowing in blue,
星空のミラーボール
is a mirror ball in the starry sky.
さあ... 私を照らして
Come now... shine a light on me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to shake the earth with a tap,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away right here.
「なんであなたにはできないの？」なんてさ
"Why can't you do it?" they say.
陰口言われたり 呆れられたり
Talked about behind my back, looked at with dismay,
口角下がるデイズ 手一杯で
days spent frowning, my hands are full.
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind,
流行りの野菜もスピード早すぎだね
Even trendy veggies go bad too fast.
ありのままの素敵さだけじゃ
Just being wonderful as I am
足りないんだ
isn't enough.
毎日死ぬほど頑張って
Trying my absolute hardest every day,
やっとここまで連れて来たんだ
I finally brought myself this far.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かって欲しくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My hardships...
不満もどうかご存じないでいてね
Please don't pretend to know my dissatisfaction either.
「きっとあなたにも出来るはず」なんてさ
"I'm sure you can do it too," they say.
言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as those words.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って
Still, trying my absolute hardest,
賭ける値打ちはあると思った
I thought there was value in betting on it.
投げ出したくなるよ
It makes me want to give up.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to quit.
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部 私だけのもの
and my failures, they all belong only to me.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かって欲しくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My hardships...
不満もどうかご存じないでいてね
Please don't pretend to know my dissatisfaction either.
【お弁当】差し入れ参加者様
[Lunchbox] Gift Contributors
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone who sent gifts!
Na na na...
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
胸に詰め込んだ夢はくしゃくしゃで
My dreams packed in my chest are crumpled
勇気がいるけど
It takes courage, but
【フラスタ】差し入れ参加者様
[Flower Stand] Gift Contributors
君にだけは見せたい
I want to show only you
予想外かな
Is it unexpected?
一緒に行けるかな
Can we go together?
秘密の...渡して
Handing over the secret...
深呼吸して
Take a deep breath
分かったこと
And what I realized
壮大で
It's magnificent
笑っちゃうくらい
Enough to make me laugh
最高の一瞬を
The best moment
うまくいかない日だって
Even on days that don't go well
即興で歌う
I'll sing impromptu
明日の教科書 水に落としたら
If I drop tomorrow's textbook in the water
何だってやれそうだ
I feel like I can do anything
落書きのない壁
A wall without scribbles
想いを
My feelings
君とこうして
Like this with you
交わし合えたら
If we can exchange them
嘘みたいだな
It feels like a lie
もっと
More
瞬いて
Shine
記して
Mark it
3つ数えたら
If I count to three
砂に書いた絵
A picture drawn in the sand
消えてしまうけど
It will disappear, but
それと同じで
It's the same as that
君の顔ばかり
Nothing but your face
浮かべてたら
If I keep picturing it
アイスみたいに溶けて
Melting like ice cream
夢も愛もキュッとしていっぱいだから
Dreams and love are squeezed tight, so I'm full
だから持ちきれない
So I can't hold it all
でも欲張りすぎてきっと...
But I'm too greedy, surely...
もうラクラクチュッチュ恋に落ちちゃって
Already falling into 'Rakuraku Chuchu' love
ギュッギュ戻れない
Squeeze squeeze, I can't go back
あれあれなんでふわりと心がまだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my heart still get hot and fluffy?
ラクラクチュッチュ君の重力で
Rakuraku Chuchu, with your gravity
引き寄せて
Pull me close
カレー色覗いてるみたいで
Like peeking at a kaleidoscope (curry) color
ねキラキラな未来みたい分からない
Hey, it's like a sparkling future, I don't know
青 up and down で超振り回す
Blue up and down, totally swaying me
You and the kyou wa shirokujichuu
You and today, all day long
Calendar 30 nichi demo tarinai
Even 30 days in the calendar aren't enough
Are mo kore mo sore mo zenbu shitai
I want to do this, that, and everything
キュンキュン急上昇ドクドク拍動
Heart-throbbing rapid rise, pounding heartbeat
キュンキュン急降下深呼吸
Heart-throbbing rapid drop, deep breath
キュンキュン急上昇ラブラブメーター
Heart-throbbing rapid rise, love-love meter
キュンキュン急降下突撃だ！
Heart-throbbing rapid drop, charge!
無限大の愛だけど失敗だけど諦めない
It's infinite love, a failure, but I won't give up
まだ欲張りだから君として行く
I'm still greedy, so I'll go with you
もうラクラクチュッチュ心がハマって
Already Rakuraku Chuchu, my heart is hooked
抜け出せない
Can't get out
あれあれなんで目まぐるしい心がまだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my dizzy heart still get hot?
ラクラクチュッチュスピード重視で
Rakuraku Chuchu, prioritizing speed
引き寄せて
Pull me close
カレー色覗いてるみたいで
Like peeking at a kaleidoscope (curry) color
ねキラキラな未来みたい分からない
Hey, it's like a sparkling future, I don't know
チープだけどな理想を歌うわ
It's cheap, but I'll sing my ideals
私はまだ未完成で
I'm still incomplete
あの空に目を細めてしまうんだ
I end up squinting at that sky
考えてもどうしようもないことだとか
Thinking about things that can't be helped
求めら心から
Seek from the heart
色々噛んでくるけど
Various things bite at me, but
だからこそ笑顔でね
That's why, keep smiling
だからこそ負けないで
That's why, don't give up
羽ばたくための羽を手にして
Get the wings to take flight
飛び出してくんだよ
And jump out!
空を飛んで行こう
Let's fly in the sky
飛んで行こう
Let's fly
色付いてく夢ほら未知数から
Look, dreams are coloring up from the unknown
青混ぜてみよう
Let's mix in some blue
混ぜてみよう
Let's mix it
少し大きくなったね
You've grown a little, haven't you?
空は青い色
The sky is blue
青い色
Blue color
少し経ったらすぐに茜色
After a bit, it will soon be madder red
今日と迷っても
Even if you get lost today
迷っても
Even if you get lost
ゆっくり風を受けて
Slowly feel the wind
星に願いを
Wish upon a star
なんてよく言うくせして
You often say that, but
いつしか忘れていた
I had forgotten before I knew it
奇跡の起こし方をさ
How to make miracles happen
ある時は笑顔でね
Sometimes with a smile
ある時は泣き顔で
Sometimes with a tearful face
見上げた空
The sky I looked up at
滲む景色に
In the blurry scenery
虹を見出して
Finding a rainbow
旅立っていくんだよ
We are setting off
空を飛んで行こう
Let's fly in the sky
空は暗い色
The sky is a dark color
影の色
Color of shadows
心がずっと落ち込んでしまっても
Even if my heart is down for a long time
やがては瑠璃色
Eventually it will be lapis lazuli color
青い色
Blue color
私がきっと晴れ晴れにしちゃうから
Because I'll surely make it bright and sunny
空の形色無限だね
The shape and color of the sky are infinite
巡り巡っていつかまたこの場所で
Going round and round, someday again at this place
どんな空色が
What kind of sky color
見えるかな
Will we see?
空を飛んで行こう 飛んで行こう
Let's fly in the sky, let's fly.
色づき始めた夢は止まらない
The dreams that have started to color won't stop.
もっと伝えよう 伝えよう
Let's convey it more, let's convey it.
La La La こんなメロディで
La La La, with this melody.
空は青い色 青い色
The sky is blue, blue.
少し経ったらすぐに茜色
After a little while, it immediately turns madder red.
今日の楽しさ眩しいね
Today's fun is dazzling, isn't it?
だけど温かい気持ち
But it's a warm feeling.
手を取り合って 笑い合ってくれるから
Because we hold hands and laugh together.
これからも私のことよろしくね
Please continue to support me from now on too.
今日の日をうららかに歌いながら
While singing pleasantly about today.
空を飛んで行こう 飛んで行こう
Let's fly in the sky, let's fly.
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent gifts, thank you very much!
バーチャル リアル どっちかわいい？
Virtual, Real, which is cuter?
バーチャル リアル どっちもかわいい！
Virtual, Real, both are cute!
Check it! Chu-Chu-Chu...
サムネタップ はじめまして
Tap the thumbnail, nice to meet you.
キュンとしたなら ハート押して
If your heart skipped a beat, press the heart.
通知はON
Notifications ON.
いつでもカモン
Come on anytime.
一緒に踊ろうよ
Let's dance together.
Online Now
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I want to eat sweets but I'm on a diet.
君の好みに アップデート中
Updating to your preferences.
ポチり更新
One-click update.
君と交信
Communicating with you.
もっと 推してほしいの
I want you to support me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, Real, which do you like?
つながる 一 二 三次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions.
One Two Threeで 飛び越えて
Jumping over with One Two Three.
今やネットメモリアルです
Now it's a net memorial.
チクチクしないで ラブ＆ピースで
Don't be prickly, let's go with Love & Peace.
Check it out, wa wa wa
トキメイチャ
Get excited,
時かけガール
Time leaping girl.
Two Two Three Three One
混ぜれば最強 バーチャルリアル
If mixed, it's the strongest Virtual Real.
Check it! Chu-Chu-Chu...
2番にスワイプ ビート足して
Swipe to number 2, add the beat.
キュンキュンしてなら 手叩いて
If you're throbbing, clap your hands.
ガチ勢も
Hardcore fans too,
エンジョイ勢も
casual fans too,
一緒に踊ろうよ
let's dance together.
Online Now
会話イマイチだけど コラボ中
Conversation is not great but we're collaborating.
ニュー楽しいこと リサーチ中
Researching new fun things.
ピピピ テレパシー
Pi-pi-pi Telepathy.
今日も配信
Streaming today too.
もっと ハート欲しいの
I want more hearts.
ねぇねぇ どっちかわいい？
Hey hey, which is cuter?
どっちかわいい？
Which is cuter?
ねぇねぇ どっちかわいい？
Hey hey, which is cuter?
どっちかわいい？
Which is cuter?
どっちもかわいい！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I want to eat sweets but I'm on a diet.
君の好みに アップデート中
Updating to your preferences.
ポチり更新
One-click update.
君と交信
Communicating with you.
もっと 推してほしいの
I want you to support me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, Real, which do you like?
バーチャル リアル どっちも好き
Virtual, Real, I like both.
つながる 一 二 三次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions.
One Two Threeで 飛び越えて
Jumping over with One Two Three.
今やネットメモリアルです
Now it's a net memorial.
チクチクしないで ラブ＆ピースで
Don't be prickly, let's go with Love & Peace.
Check it out, wa wa wa
トキメイチャ
Get excited,
時かけガール
Time leaping girl.
Two Two Three Three One
混ぜれば最強 バーチャルリアル
If mixed, it's the strongest Virtual Real.
Check it! Chu-Chu-Chu...
しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait for a moment.
Please wait a moment.
しばらくお待ちください。
2025.10.1 Wed
8th Anniversary Party Starry Bloomin'
ARE YOU READY
澄み渡る青空にも
Even in the clear blue sky,
間違いも強がりから
Mistakes also come from bravado.
本当は震えている
The truth is, I'm trembling,
手足が隠せないよ
I can't hide my shaking limbs.
もどかしいの先はどうも
The future of this frustration somehow...
意味のない色で描く
paints with meaningless colors.
崩れかけた昨日のこと
About the yesterday that nearly crumbled,
止められなかった昨日のこと
about the yesterday I couldn't stop.
ツバメみたいに速く
Fast like a swallow,
飛べたらいいのに
I wish I could fly.
もう何もいらないから
I don't need anything else anymore,
忘れさせてくれ
so let me forget.
どこまでも遠くへと
To somewhere endlessly far away,
連れて行って
take me there,
戻らないまま
without turning back.
Take a journey
涙を夜に
Leaving tears in the night,
あの闇を超えて
crossing that darkness.
導く翼で
With guiding wings,
もっと...
more...
みんな！
Everyone!
隠した傷跡は
The hidden scars have
滲んでしまった
blurred away.
君と大事な
With you, the precious...
君のスペシャルな夢の続き
continuation of your special dream.
子供みたいに青く
Blue like a child,
願い叶いのに
even though the wish came true.
気がつけば檻の中
Before I knew it, inside a cage,
奏でて...
playing music...
目の隅で光った
Shining in the corner of my eye,
同じ夢を見た
we dreamed the same dream.
君と大事なものだから
Because it's precious with you,
間違っても
even if we make mistakes,
彷徨っても
even if we wander,
話さないでいいよ
you don't have to speak.
空の果て
The end of the sky,
その先を見つめて
gazing at what lies beyond.
飛びたいの
I want to fly.
この命かけて
Betting this life...
もっともっと！
More, more!
ありのまま紡いで
Spinning it just as it is,
一つだけ
just one thing,
涙色の想い 闇を超えて
crossing the darkness with tear-colored thoughts.
いつだってそばにいるよ
I'm always by your side.
ずっと
Always...
夢の先へ 空へ
beyond the dream, to the sky.
La la la...
高鳴る心臓に祈りを乗せて
Entrusting a prayer to my throbbing heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
I sketch a vague dream.
幻想は想像のまま
Illusions remain just imaginations,
終われないんだ
but I can't let it end.
答えを延々と探し続けて
Endlessly continuing to search for the answer,
何者かになりたくて
wanting to become someone.
散々と降る夕立を
The evening shower that falls incessantly,
ただ眺めた
I just gazed at it.
優しく寄り添って
Gently snuggling close,
心が晴れるのなら
if my heart clears up,
翼が生えたようで
it's as if wings have grown,
気がして
I feel like that.
いつだって隣にいるから
Because I'm always by your side.
だって
Because...
言葉紡いで歌うことが
spinning words and singing
私の運命だ
is my destiny.
世界にありふれた
Common in the world,
虚しささえも
even the emptiness,
上書きして
overwriting it.
路地裏に咲いた花のように
Like a flower blooming in the back alley,
願いを照らす
illuminating the wish,
小さな光に憧れて
longing for a small light.
名前を持たない歌なんて
A song without a name,
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge it.
一つ一つ
One by one,
枯れない花のよう
like an unfading flower,
昨日の自分にさよならして
saying goodbye to yesterday's self.
溢れた涙
Overflowing tears...
うまく笑えなくてもいいかな
Is it okay if I can't smile well?
だって
Because...
理想は遠ざかってくばかり
ideals just keep getting further away,
もう散々だよ
it's already too much.
どれだけ手を伸ばして
No matter how much I reach out
叫んだって
and shout,
届かないの
it won't reach.
望めばいつか
If I wish, someday...
叶うはずって信じてる
I believe it will come true.
どうか歌よ響いて
Please, song, echo!
あぁ心臓の鼓動が今日も五月蝿い
Ah, my heart's beating is noisy again today.
行き止まりばっか
Nothing but dead ends,
足が竦んで立てないよ
my legs are frozen and I can't stand.
音のない世界から
From a world without sound,
君を見つけて
I'll find you
連れ出すんだ
and take you away.
言葉紡いで歌うことが
Spinning words and singing
私の運命だ
is my destiny.
世界にありふれた
Common in the world,
虚しささえも
even the emptiness,
上書きして
overwriting it.
路地裏に咲いた花のように
Like a flower blooming in the back alley,
願いを照らす
illuminating the wish,
小さな光に憧れて
longing for a small light.
君の歌姫になれたらいいな
I hope I can become your diva.
さぁ始まるAdventure
Now, the adventure begins.
Rally Rally
8光年先の未来
The future 8 light years away,
誰もが求めるウェルネス
the wellness everyone seeks,
8次元まで飛んじゃって
flying to the 8th dimension.
地球ごと 何度失敗したって
Even if the whole Earth fails again and again,
アバンチュール パリパリ
Aventure, Party Party!
あっという間に時代はグルリの終わり
In a flash, the era turns around and ends.
宇宙を走れ さあ
Run through space, come on!
時代創造して
Create a new era.
さあ 次の波へ
Now, onto the next wave.
さあ 無限大の可能性へ
Now, to infinite possibilities!
と と と...
Fly, fly, fly...
飛んでって ビビビ
Fly away, bi-bi-bi!
巡って 回る回るずっと
Going around, spinning spinning forever.
まだまだ 終わらない
It's not over yet!
踊れ踊れ 飛んでって ビビビ
Dance, dance! Fly away, bi-bi-bi!
巡って 回る回るずっと
Going around, spinning spinning forever.
ここから気づく今日
Realizing it from here, today...
私 インフィニティの先へ
I'm heading beyond infinity!
ララ ララララ
La la, la la la la...
輝くの さあ ぜんぶ脱ぎ捨て
It's shining! Now, cast everything off!
ララ ララララ
La la, la la la la...
輝くことなく愛を
Love without limit to the shine...
ててて それ更新中！
Te-te-te... updating now!
一人じゃ行けない
I can't go there alone,
所まで
to that place.
見せて見せる
I'll show you, I'll show it,
フューチャー
the Future!
見とけ！
Watch me!
ハイ！
Hai!
さあ 時代を超えて
Now, crossing the eras,
さあ 今の声
now, this voice of the present.
さあ 巡り続け
Now, keep circulating,
ずっとずっと
forever and ever.
続けて
Keep going!
飛んでって ビビビ
Fly away, bi-bi-bi!
エネルギーと 君とのメロディ
The energy and the melody with you.
一緒に見た夢
The dream we saw together,
ここに 秘め
hidden right here.
脈上がり始めた
My pulse has started to rise,
永久の先へ
towards eternity!
飛んでって ビビビ
Fly away, bi-bi-bi!
巡って 回る回るずっと
Going around, spinning spinning forever.
まだまだ 終わらない
It's not over yet!
踊れ踊れ 飛んでって ビビビ
Dance, dance! Fly away, bi-bi-bi!
巡って 回る回るずっと
Going around, spinning spinning forever.
ここから気づく今日
Realizing it from here, today...
私 インフィニティの先へ
I'm heading beyond infinity!
ララ ララララ
La la, la la la la...
輝くの さあ ぜんぶ脱ぎ捨て
It's shining! Now, cast everything off!
ララ ララララ
La la, la la la la...
輝くことなく愛を
Love without limit to the shine...
ててて それ更新中！
Te-te-te... updating now!
はい みんな ボンソメ！
Alright everyone, Bon-some!
みんなの声が大きすぎて オケが聞こえないレベルの大歓声 ありがとう
The cheers were so huge I couldn't hear the music! Thank you!
ちょっとイヤモニ着けて 笑っちゃった
I actually laughed a bit while wearing my ear monitor.
ということで 一年半ぶりの
So, it's been a year and a half...
有観客なんですけど
since I've had an audience.
本当 亡霊のやついるんか？ えっと...
Are there really ghosts out there? Umm...
みんなー！
Everyone!
って言って「はーい」とか言ってみてください いきますよ
Please say 'Hai' or something when I call. Here we go!
男の子！
Boys!
ちょっと恥ずかしいかもしれない ちょっと手だけ振ってもいいよ
It might be a little embarrassing. You can just wave your hand.
女の子！
Girls!
おお！声 聞こえた ありがとう！
Ooh! I heard your voices, thank you!
海外の方！
People from overseas!
おお すごい！
Ooh, amazing!
そして そうだな
And, let's see...
めちゃ遠くから来たよって人 絶対自分が一番遠いみたいな...
Anyone who came from really far away? Like 'I'm definitely the furthest'...
いる？ あ でも海外の方かな？ ありがとうございます
Anyone? Ah, maybe the overseas folks? Thank you.
そして... そうだな... ミステリー席の方！
And... let's see... people in the Mystery Seats!
いぇーい ありがとうございます！
Yaaay! Thank you very much!
では みんなで行くよ
Now, let's do it with everyone.
みんな！
Everyone!
こっち側！
This side!
That side!
最後に... 全員！
Lastly... Everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい ということで これがね やりたかったのずっと
Yes, so... I've wanted to do this for a long time.
はいっ！
Okay!
というわけでですね、なんと、
So, with that said, actually...
YouTubeで見てる皆さん？
everyone watching on YouTube?
無料配信はここまでなんです。
The free stream ends here.
えっ、今来たばっかり？
Eh, you just got here?
私も今来たばっかり。
I just got here too.
そうだよね、わかるわかる。
That's right, isn't it? I get it, I get it.
え、わかってるよ。
Eh, I know.
コメントのみんなも見えてるよ。
I can see everyone's comments too.
イェイッて言ってるなぁ。
You're saying "Yay".
イェ…うん、ちょっとラグってるのかもしれない。
Ya... hm, it might be lagging a bit.
今来たばっかりって書いてね。
Write "I just got here", okay?
よろしく。
Thanks.
続きは、えー、見たい人、
For those who want to see the rest,
概要欄から見てもらえると。
you can check the description.
どこにあるのかな？
I wonder where it is?
どっかに概要欄のタグあるよって。
They say the description tag is somewhere.
そこら辺からちょっと見てもらえれば、
If you could check around there,
嬉しいです！
I'd be happy!
やば。
Whoops.
ちょっと。
Wait.
次の曲いっちゃおうかな？
Shall I go to the next song?
まだまだ盛り上がれる？
Can you still get hyped?
みんながお家に帰ってくるの、
Everyone coming home,
待ってたよ。
I was waiting for it.
というわけで、次の曲は、
So, the next song is,
新アルバムから、
from the new album,
この曲です！
this song!
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The free introductory stream ends here.
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ >> SPWN
★Purchase live tickets here >> SPWN